A little pause... and we are back.
A little pause...
and we are back.
A little pause... and we are back.
Hey, you want to see it, don't you?
I'd say it's time.
For what?
Come on, you know what I'm talking about.
Kakashi Sensei's real face!
What's the matter with you?
Please, this is lame.
You can count me out.
We finished today's mission.
I'm out of here.
Yeah, you're totally right.
Who am I kidding?
This sounds fun.
What if he has lips?
Like a blimp!
Just one more little push!
Or maybe buck teeth?
Buck teeth!
Or maybe buck teeth!
Well, this is out of the ordinary.
Here, thanks for waiting.
The three of you treating me to lunch?
I wouldn't be surprised if it snowed on
me.
He fell for it!
You know what I mean?
Here, thanks for waiting.
The three of you treating me to lunch?
I wouldn't be surprised if it snowed on
me.
Today.
Or something.
He fell for it!
Is that the idea?
Here, thanks for waiting.
The three of you treating me to lunch?
You're not gonna drop a big pile of snow
on me, are you?
Or something like that?
No, I'm just being silly.
Got to play rock-paper-scissors.
He fell for it!
Well...
Come on, you guys are up to something,
right?
What are you, crazy?
Kashi-sensei, please, you just get out of
the hospital.
Now please, why don't you just go ahead
and eat?
Well, all right then.
I suppose I should just dig in.
Thank you for waiting.
The roasted pork is on us!
Boy,
this looks good.
Hey, Sasuke!
What are the horses doing?
Get out of the way, Ino-pig!
Ah, man!
I can't see Squad!
All done.
That was tasty.
So fast!
Something wrong?
No, of course not!
What makes you say that?
What the...
Okay,
now I'm curious!
What?
Seriously?
We're gonna catch another cat?
Well, not quite.
You're actually after Nekomata.
And your mission is not to capture him,
but to get a paw print from him.
Ah!
Nekomata, Mt.
Lion, cute little kitty cat, whatever it
is.
This is just a D-rank mission,
so no thanks.
I say, just let someone else handle
small-time stuff like this.
Right, Sasuke?
I mean, aren't you tired of lame missions
like this one?
Go on, tell him!
Uh, Sasuke?
You don't have to come along if you don't
want to.
This isn't Uchiha.
No, wait.
My mission.
But why?
I'm glad you've come, Sasuke-boy.
It's been a long time, Granny Cat.
My, you're all grown up.
You know her, Sasuke?
She's weird.
What kind of place is this?
This shop is where the Uchiha clan
traditionally buys all its weapons.
Granny Cat also provides intel for the
Uchiha, and she's our client for this mission.
Tamaki!
Get the poor encyclopedia and bring it to
me.
Sure thing.
Here you are, Grandma.
You bound all of them into a book?
You know, Sasuke, you
sure do seem to know a
whole lot more about
this mission than we do.
I think you'd better start doing some
explaining.
This book started as a game between Sasuke
and his brother.
Itachi!
Don't talk about Itachi!
I'm gonna start preparing for the mission.
So what was that all about?
They used to be so close back then.
I remember.
Itachi would often come by on errands and
bring little Sasuke in tow.
Sasuke would get bored, throw tantrums,
and give Itachi such a hard time.
So Itachi came up with a game for him to
play.
He had Sasuke chase down
all the quick and nimble cats
he could catch, and then
gather paw prints from them.
It was a silly kid's game.
Yes, I suppose.
But remember, Sasuke
already had the skills
of a genin even before
he entered the academy.
From the start, he was an uchiha through
and through.
In any event, it was merely a cute game at
first.
But things quickly began to escalate.
Sasuke completed
nearly all the assignments
Itachi gave him, even
the ones given half in jest.
And then we collected
his stockpile of paw
prints and compiled
them all into this book.
But even though Sasuke no longer plays the
game, something about it bothers me.
Sasuke never completed two of the
assignments Itachi gave to him.
One was me of the Hidden Cloud, but I asked
for her paw print and she kindly agreed.
Me of the Hidden Cloud?
What's that?
Let me guess, you're asking us to go and
get the final paw print, is that it?
Yes, however, the
print you're after is from
Nekomata, a big player in
the Ninja Cat underworld.
He never shows his face in public.
His hideout is an impregnable fortress.
And he's guarded by a seemingly endless
amount of Ninja Cats.
Can a three-man team of genin handle
something so hard?
Are you kidding me?
We've handled way worse than this.
Just leave it to us.
Right, Sakura?
Keep in mind that Itachi
thought this assignment was
too dangerous for Sasuke
and wouldn't allow him to go.
You'll have to be very careful.
So that's what was bothering Sasuke.
This whole thing with his brother.
Whatever limits he set for me,
I'll go far beyond them.
Hey!
Sasuke!
Come on, let's transform into cats and
sneak into that guy's house!
I guess the best way to infiltrate a
fortress of cats is to become a cat.
Transformation jutsu!
What kind of cat looks like that?
Aww.
But I actually thought it looked pretty
good.
But you don't need to transform,
Meow.
And transforming won't let you understand
cat speech, Meow.
So, here you go.
If you put these on, the cats will think
you're one of them.
And you'll understand them.
If it's that simple, then why didn't you
just give us these from the very start?
I actually have to wear this thing?
We're known in these parts, so I'm afraid
we can't go any further, Meow.
No ninja cat has ever seen Nekomata's
face.
Do you think you'll be able to find him,
Meow?
Thanks to these, infiltrating his fortress
shouldn't really be a problem.
You look so cute in those, Sasuke.
If we can get inside his stronghold,
then the rest will be no problem.
Come on.
Let's go.
Wait.
Hold it.
Sasuke, look.
We're supposed to be able to talk to ninja
cats if we wear these.
And that means you won't have to go start
a fight with this Nekomata guy.
Let's just talk to him about it.
I bet that he'd be willing to give you a
paw print or two.
Impossible.
What?
But, Meow!
Having your paw print taken is extremely
embarrassing for a cat, Meow.
He'd never allow it.
For a human, it's just like
someone stripping off your
clothes and taking a
photograph of you naked, Meow.
A naked photograph, is that all?
You just have to sweet-talk someone into
doing something like that.
I mean, I bet I could even get Sakura to
do it.
Meow, Sakura?
You big pervert!
I doubt talking will do you any good,
Meow.
Alright, well, thanks for showing us the
way, Meow.
Get going, pervert, Meow.
Meow.
Who's next?
I haven't seen you guys before,
Meow.
We're newbie cats, Meow.
Here.
For someone new, you're quick to catch on
to the way things work here, Meow.
But what gave us away?
Who knows?
It's time for us to give you your reward.
This is how we welcome new kitties,
Meow.
What's the matter?
You're welcome to play with them,
Meow.
Guys, play alone or they'll get
suspicious.
Go on.
Meow.
I can't believe I have to do this to get
that paw print.
You know, this is fun.
Achoo!
Stupid sneeze.
Anyway, Meow, this is fun.
Meow.
There's a human in our midst, and he's
trying to sneak inside.
Huh?
What are you meowing about?
I'm a cat.
Meow.
You idiot.
Let's go.
Hey, those two probably aren't cats
either.
More impostors.
Alert!
Sasuke?
Sakura, come back!
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow, meow,
meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
Okay, okay, calm down.
I'm guessing what you're saying is that
you want me to leave, right?
Okay, I'm going.
I guess it's back to the drawing board.
Meow, meow, meow!
What's with this increased security?
Does anyone know what's going on,
Meow?
I heard some humans slipped in past the
guards, Meow.
If they come close,
I'll catch them, and I'll
show them a thing
or two while I'm at it.
Meow.
Don't worry about Naruto.
I'm sure he's fine.
Let's take advantage of this commotion and
search for Nekomata.
Sakura, you go look to the east.
I'll go west.
Huh?
But we have to stick together if this is
gonna work.
They already know that we're inside the
fortress.
Time's of the essence.
Right now, it's smarter to split up to
look.
Oh, okay.
Let's do it.
What's all the commotion out there,
Meow?
Boss, a couple of humans got past the
guards and infiltrated the fortress, Meow.
What, human intruders?
Find them and get rid of them this
instant, Meow.
Yes, sir, Meow.
A human in my stronghold?
It's been seven years since the last time.
No, it couldn't be, Meow.
If I can't go through the front gate,
I'll just sneak in from the side.
I am a ninja, after all.
The best place to get information is a
bar.
Your catnip drink, miss, Meow.
Thanks, but I didn't actually order
anything yet, Meow.
Compliments to that customer.
Hello.
May I come and join you, Meow?
Oh, sure.
Well, always nice to meet someone new.
How about a little treat?
You simply must try this, Meow.
Excuse me.
By any chance, do you happen to know a cat
named Nekomata?
Boss, yeah.
He always stays in the main tower.
Oh, thank you very much.
Have this if you want, Meow.
Really?
Rigged plastic bottles?
These are supposed to be used against
cats, not by them!
Boss is in the main tower.
There.
We know and we're beaten.
We surrender.
Meow.
So, you managed to make it all the way
here.
Who are you, Meow?
You're the one they call Nekomata.
It'll be easier if you volunteer your paw
print.
Otherwise, it's going to get painful.
I'm impressed that you
have the guts to stand
before me and make a
threat like that, Meow.
However...
What is this?
Who are you?
Meow!
Sounds like there is a story behind this.
Huh?
Since the first day, Nekomata has killed
me.
I want to be a part of the story.
You're my brother.
I don't think I can help.
A first-class house.
Yes, sir.
You are not alone.
I am.
BEGONE!
Mission Accomplished.
I'd say you certainly drew an unlucky hand
of cards that time, Nekomata.
Nah, I wanted to have a go with Itachi's
brother, so I could see what he was made of.
Besides, I couldn't refuse a request from
Itachi, now could I?
You mewnster!
In time, my kid brother will come to see
you.
And when he does, I want you to fight him
with all your might.
He probably won't have the strength to
defeat you yet.
Then why do it?
Because growth occurs when one is pushed
beyond his limits.
That knowledge is a vital part of
training.
I hate to admit it,
but when he faced me,
Sasuke passed Itachi's
test with flying colors.
Indeed, I agree with you.
But it's so unfortunate.
Those two boys were so close when they
were young.
I don't want to see
them fight each other,
but I don't want to see
them fight each other.
That's it!
Nothing's going to stop me from seeing
that face!
Yeah, but how?
You got any ideas?
Don't you worry.
We'll see it one way or another!
I'm asking you how, you stupid little
troll!
All right, smarty pants, how do you
propose we do it?
Well, we...
We'll just have to tail him around for the
day.
He'll take off the mask eventually.
Oh, Sasuke, I swear you are so smart!
Oh, whatever.
Good plan, Captain.
Captain Obvious!
I'm sorry, what was that?
Uh, never mind.
What in the world is Kakashi-sensei doing?
It's so disappointing.
He's onto us.
Naruto, you idiot, you blew our cover!
Why the heck is it my fault?
Wait.
My favorite book is going to be a movie?
I better order tickets in advance!
Hey, he's on the move!
Let's go before we lose him.
Yeah, right!
He's gone!
Oh, great, he got away.
Are you kidding?
Where did he vanish off to?
Hey, what are you three doing?
Do you guys need me for something?
No, not really!
Hmm...
This thing has the
creepiest eyes, like it's always
thinking about trying
to eat me or something.
Oh, don't be ridiculous.
I think it's kind of cute.
Anyway, you're the one who drew the short
stick, so you're just going to have to
take care of it until we get back to the
village.
If it's any consolation, you two make
quite a cute couple.
How can you say this thing is cute?
Ow!
Quick, cut it out!
Come on!
First it was a stray cat.
Then a stray dog and a pig.
Now it's a stray ostrich.
Well, we may be going up
in size, but I don't see how
these silly missions are
supposed to improve our skills.
Missions, huh?
The purpose of these missions isn't to
improve your skills.
You're not doing this for training.
Although I understand why you may be
getting impatient.
Hey, here's an idea.
Why don't you improve your skills by
taking care of this ostrich?
Hey, what do you think you're doing,
Naruto?
Just shut up and take care of it!
That bird is only your responsibility!
Stop doing that!
Not your face!
Stop it!
We'll find an inn for the night so we can
rest up.
Even Mr. Ostrich here looks worn out.
All right.
We could have made it
back to the village tonight
if someone did a
better job with that bird.
Huh?
What's going on?
I better go check it out!
Hey, don't run off again!
Let's go.
What could be happening?
Not you guys, too.
It's just a fight?
No, it seems to be a vendetta.
A vendetta?
Like when someone fights to get revenge or
to right a wrong?
Revenge, huh?
On a busy street in the middle of the day,
they allow that, Kakashi-sensei?
Hmm.
A vendetta permit, huh?
It varies from village to village,
but sometimes if someone is murdered,
family members are allowed to seek
revenge.
If he has an authorized
permit from a land where the
crime took place, other
nations will allow the vendetta.
I heard that Tsukado,
the guy with the
vendetta, had a distant
relative who was killed.
Yeah, late one night his opponent went to
visit the victim.
Then he ruthlessly hit Tsukado's relative
with a rock and killed him.
It's an awful story, isn't it?
Anyway, the killer escaped and the family
wanted revenge.
They chose Tsukado to handle it.
Then that coward deserves what he gets!
Kanaboon, it looks like a vendetta,
boss.
Hmm.
Now this is interesting.
Tell me what you think, boys.
Who's gonna win?
Well, I've heard it said that the hunter
is often stronger than the hunted.
Heh.
Nah, I can't go along with you on that
one.
That hunted one has a pretty mean look
about him, if you ask me.
Hmm.
Aaaaah!
There they go!
Oh no!
What the...
Looks like he won't be getting his revenge
today.
What the hell?
Hey, come back here!
Hey, stop!
Stop, you bastard!
Damn you, bastard!
Here.
Oh, my sword.
Thank you.
He sure got lucky that time.
I almost had him.
Really?
Cause it didn't look that way to me.
Hmph.
Amateurs should keep their opinions to
themselves.
You can't tell by looking at me,
but I am the veteran of 34 vendettas.
Oh, I see.
Wait, what?
You mean you failed at this 34 times?
Next time for sure.
I doubt that, bud!
There is no way to know if I can win
unless I try.
So I'll try again.
You know what they say, 35th time's the
charm!
Right.
Okay, I get it!
Huh?
I'll help you and I won't take no for an
answer!
Huh?
Yeah!
I'm gonna use every
single ninja skill I have
to help you become
a real pro at vendettas!
Huh?
He's getting carried away again,
like always!
Well, why don't we let Naruto handle this
one on his own?
We can go rest up at the inn.
Ridiculous.
Leave it to me and that vendetta's as good
as done!
Mm-mm.
Lesson one!
You don't have anywhere near enough anger
toward your enemy!
You literally have to be ready to explode
with anger at any given moment!
Cause then you'll never be caught off
guard for a vendetta!
Uh, okay...
Hey you, old lady!
Look, you really need to be more careful!
Come on, hurry up and get on my back!
Now, tell me where you want to go,
dammit!
The next town, huh?
Alright, I'm glad to help out!
Uh, that isn't... If it's
farther, that's fine!
Oh boy...
Lesson two!
Take all vendettas seriously, even easy
ones!
Get used to revenge!
Uh... Excuse me, sir!
I shall assist you.
What?
Ahhh!
Ha!
Take that!
We'll cut it out!
You stop it!
That's not what I meant either!
Think again!
Quit it!
Alright, lesson three!
Completely fill your mind with pictures of
your enemy!
And then put your anger down on paper!
Uh-huh...
What?
What's wrong with you?
You can't make your most hated enemy look
so nice at you!
You know, I gotta say, mister...
I don't really think you're cut out for
vendettas at all.
Yeah, and you're not really cut out to be
a coach.
Do you have to do it?
Carry out the vendetta?
I do.
I can't go back to my village until it's
finished.
I just want all of this to end,
so I can go home.
My elderly mother and father need me.
An ostrich is running wild!
An ostrich?
Whoa, mister... That swordsman...
he was hiding his skills.
Alright, boys!
Yes, sir!
Time for some fun.
Sorry, the ostrich bit through his leash.
Just as I suspected, you are actually a
master swordsman.
He's what?
Hey, what's going on here?
If you're really that good with your sword,
how come you can't finish your vendetta?
I don't know.
But whenever I look into his eyes,
all of my strength drains out of me.
It's those eyes.
Those piercing eyes.
Mister...
Ugh... I wonder where
that vendetta guy ran off to.
He probably set out early in pursuit of
his enemy.
Will he do that for the rest of his life?
What's going on?
Well, what do you think, mister vendetta?
Your tenacity has won me over.
I want to make sure you get your revenge,
so I brought your enemy right to you.
I'm guessing you want to give him the
payback he deserves, right?
Focus, mister.
Wait.
We, the Kanabun gang, will oversee this
vendetta and ensure its fairness.
All right, everyone, here we go.
Who do you think's gonna win?
We're taking all bets.
Which one's stronger?
I say the one out for revenge.
That guy's hopeless.
The way he'll win.
Well, I'm betting 500 on the other guy.
Me too.
If anyone's short on cash, the Kanabun
gang will place a bet for you.
If that Tsukado guy uses his real
strength, this fight won't last a minute.
Yeah, and we'll make a tidy profit.
That's terrible.
Those guys are just trying to make a buck
off this vendetta.
It all ends right here.
Sorry, but I'm not just going to lay down
and give up.
On guard.
What?
He's trying to fight without looking his
opponent in the eye.
He might actually win.
Wait, did Naruto's lessons actually help?
There's something about this fight that's
bugging me.
Something's off.
What is it?
What's on the other side of his helmet?
It's him.
Just like Mister said.
It's that guy's face.
Those eyes.
Those eyes again!
How can you look at me like that?
And you don't know that I could kill you!?
B suck.
Just give me a second.
I know the reason why you couldn't kill
this guy.
And I'm betting that somewhere deep down
inside of you, you know it too.
Of course.
I understand now.
I see.
His blade has been dulled.
He couldn't kill anyone with it even if he
wanted to.
Let me explain.
I have a twin brother who is named Kageki.
Are you serious?
A twin brother?
Yes.
Kageki had loaned money to Shikazo,
a member of your clan.
But then my brother had
a child and needed money
quickly, so he went to
Shikazo to ask to be repaid.
Shikazo ignored my brother and tried to
back out of his debt.
They argued, a scuffle broke out between
them, and they both fell to the dirt floor.
But when he fell, Shikazo hit his head on
a stone.
And then he died.
Are you saying it was all just an
accident?
Kageki said that he'd turn himself in.
But there were no witnesses to back him
up.
Given the circumstances, he probably would
have been accused of murder.
So I offered to switch places with him.
You did what?
I assumed my twin brother's identity.
And then I told him, his
wife, and their newborn
child to go into hiding
to keep them all safe.
In order to buy them
time to escape, I purposely
attracted the attention
of the pursuers.
I couldn't let a great guy like him ruin
his own life.
Not when I'm such a scoundrel.
Who's caused nothing but grief to my
family, and to society.
I guess I figured that this would be a
way...
To atone for all that.
I only have my brother's word about it.
There's no way for me to prove that's what
happened.
But I believe that what he said is true.
Hm.
Mister?
But it's up to you whether you want to
believe me or not.
And if you don't believe me...
Then you can kill me.
I'm going to choose to believe that what
you say is the truth.
You... Yeah, Mister!
Frankly, I'm sick and tired of this thing
called revenge.
If you've pretended all these years to be
my enemy...
Well then, I'll just pretend to be on a
vendetta.
Thank you.
You think everything turned out okay,
Kakashi-sensei?
Well...
That's for those two to decide.
I guess revenge is really complicated,
isn't it?
Hmph.
What would you know about it?
Huh?
Sometimes a vendetta must be carried out
no matter how hard it is.
Hey.
How'd you figure out we were tailing him,
huh?
Maybe there were just too many of us.
Oh, please.
If you know how to hide, it doesn't matter
how many people there are.
Don't tell me you've forgotten all of your
jutsu, Sakura!
You're the one who forgets!
We should shadow him.
It'll be good practice.
But we should do it solo this time.
Yeah, I think so too.
We should totally ditch Naruto.
Say what?!
Hmm...
Forlorn, Junko fell on him.
I'm losing you, and in doing so,
I am lost.
Huh?
What the... Hey!
I... Wha... Ah!
Hm?
He got away.
Just as clumsy as always.
Why are you such an idiot?
Ugh... Ugh...
Hm?
What?
Kikiki!
Wh... Huh?
Right...
Don't you see!
What is he doing?
Ugh... Huh?
What?
Huh?
Sasuke, how'd it go?
I got tired of shadowing him.
Listen and enjoy, people of the Leaf
Village.
I've come to provide a
moment's respite from
life's hardships with some
festive song and dance.
Honore...
Good job on that mission, guys.
Yeah, we're great.
But what's really great is that I can
finally get some Ichiraku ramen.
That does sound good.
Naruto, it's your treat, right?
What?
Oh, alright.
I guess so.
Wait a sec.
Sasuke, how about you treating us for
once?
Huh.
I'm gonna go train, not eat.
What about you, Kakashi-sensei?
That woman is so beautiful.
And a criminal, apparently.
I've heard she's a Kunoichi
who disguised herself as a street
performer so she could
gather intel on the land of fire.
So she's actually a spy?
What happens now?
Well, she'll be interrogated so we can
discover exactly what she learned.
They'll use any and all means at their
disposal until she confirms it.
And then she confesses what she knows.
Welcome, come in.
We call this the Honesty Room.
Hmm.
She must be quite well
trained indeed if she's
able to resist your
interrogation techniques.
Not one scream escaped her.
All we heard was the sound of her gritting
her teeth.
My, what an impressive Kunoichi.
Well then, we'll just
have to reach into that
silence and listen to
her inner voice instead.
I understand, sir.
Please summon him for me.
Clouds.
They look like clouds.
Just like the ones we saw that day.
We're all finished using pain.
It's time for a gentler approach.
Now, Hanare.
Your task is to infiltrate
the Land of Fire and
report back on the
state of affairs in the Leaf.
I'm to go to the Hidden Leaf Village?
Our nation has survived all these years
not because of our military might,
but rather due to our skill at espionage.
We gather all of the information we can
from the other nations, use it to plan
strategies, and gain advantage over
opponents in negotiations.
That way, we can avert potential
conflicts.
The fate of our nation now rests in your
hands, Hanare.
Yes, sir.
I will not fail.
What's that?
That headband?
The Hidden Lock Village.
In the Land of Ki.
We captured her before she was able to
reach the Leaf Village.
She didn't learn anything of importance.
And now, it's my turn to get some intel on
your village and why you were sent here.
What's going on?
Why doesn't she have any memories of her
own village?
It was nothing.
What?
Memories of me as a child?
Yeah.
Do you remember anything about her?
No.
I've never met her before.
Oh, I see.
Did you learn anything else?
Nothing significant.
She seems to have no memories of the
Hidden Lock Village at all.
I'm guessing that she purged them.
Purged them?
But something else is bothering me.
Something I can't quite put my finger on.
And it's more than just the fact that she
had memories of you.
She's hiding something.
Something even I can't dig up.
I'm baffled.
That's why you're here.
I need your help with this, Kakashi.
Huh?
Me?
But I'm not a member of the intel
division.
You might be able to see deeper into her
psyche than we can.
You must be some kind of fool.
You're showing me around the very village
I infiltrated to spy on.
You won't see anything here you wouldn't
see in any other village.
And I thought you could use some air after
being in that stuffy room.
Hmm.
Which flower should I choose?
What?
No way!
Wait a minute, what did you just say?
Oh my, Kakashi-sensei!
Kakashi's with her?
So you're curious too, huh?
It's not like that, you idiot.
Hey!
It's that woman!
What's he doing with someone like her?
Hey!
You don't have to keep your distance.
I promise I won't try to get information
out of you.
I was just asked to spend the day with
you.
That's all.
And once the day is done, so is my
assignment.
What will happen to me?
I don't know.
That cloud... looks like Naruto to me.
And next to that one is... Sasuke,
maybe.
Serious?
When I look at the clouds, I see my mother
and father who gave life to me.
Although I never knew them.
When things were hard, when I was sad,
I'd always look up at the clouds.
I'd stare at them and let my imagination
run free.
I'd daydream about
the village where I was
born, and imagine what
my parents might be like.
Those daydreams helped
me endure my loneliness,
and the pain of not
knowing a home or family.
It was the only way I could accept being
just a spy.
I can't hear anything!
They both seem so perfect for each other,
don't they?
Ridiculous.
I'm gonna get closer so I can hear!
I wasn't allowed to have a home.
I was raised outside the
village, so that I couldn't
divulge any information
about it if I were captured.
All this time, I've risked
my life on missions
for a homeland that I've
never even seen before.
That's why having a home and people who
accept me is so important.
Why are you telling me all this now,
when you've been silent all day?
Because... there's something that you've
taught me.
I knew the moment I saw you... that you
were the boy from my past.
I had decided to meet my parents.
And so I set out.
I set out for my village.
But I got lost.
I was feeling helpless when we met.
You told me that... whenever I was feeling
sad, I should look up at the clouds.
That as the clouds changed shape,
I could turn them into whatever I wanted.
You promised me that
as long as I had hope,
the clouds would give
me the comfort I needed.
From then on... I searched
the clouds for your likeness.
That's why I recognized you right away.
Even though time had changed you.
Because you've always been in my heart.
You gave me hope when things were darkest.
Whoa!
Things are really starting to heat up!
Careful!
Or else they'll... Whoa!
What are you three doing?
Oh, well, you see, Narza...
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's go!
There you go!
Congratulations!
Huh?
Thank you.
We've received news that the Hidden Lock
has captured Riichi, one of our Jonin.
The Hidden Lock Village.
We think the spy comes from there.
That Kunoichi.
Yes, Hanare.
And the Lock Village has proposed that we
exchange her for Riichi.
Fortunately for us, it appears
that she's gathered very little
information about the Land
of Fire and our Leaf Village.
So releasing her would be harmless.
Huh?
No, you can't.
I mean... I'm completely opposed to giving
her back.
Hm?
It's not a transformation, Jutsu!
That's Riichi!
Without a doubt!
Hm.
All right, then!
One man from each side will accompany
their prisoner to the center of the bridge!
And that's where we'll make the exchange!
Agreed?
Agreed.
Kakashi-sensei...
I never thought it would end like this.
I won't let you go.
Hanare!
Make sure you bring back the intel on the
hidden leaf!
Retreat!
Quick!
It's already started!
Give it up!
There's no escape, old man!
Don't underestimate the ninja of the lock.
Once a key turns the lock closed,
not even death can open it!
The blade of the deadly knife is never a
secret!
I am out of here!
Take that!
Kagashi-sensei!
You scared me!
Where's Hanare?
I guess she felt cornered and had no other
recourse.
She threw herself off the cliff.
She was an admirable ninja.
She did what?
But you... you can't be okay with this,
Kakashi-sensei.
I mean, what if that
lady really was in love
with you, and you guys
could have... Enough.
It doesn't matter now.
Off we go!
Our mission is helping out at a farm.
The mission itself's no big deal.
No matter what happens, we're gonna see
it!
Kakashi-sensei's real face!
What's with you guys today?
You seem ready for anything.
Oh, we're ready, alright!
Alrighty then.
Good to hear.
So, I've finally found you.
Kakashi Hatake.
Oh, Kakashi.
It's been a long time.
But my revenge is finally at hand.
Your revenge?
For what, boss?
You fool!
Have you forgotten?
Well, I haven't.
It was three years ago, in the spring.
No!
There's no need to be frightened!
Our boss says he has something he needs to
talk to you about.
Your boss?
I love you.
Marry me, I beg of you.
Wow, boss!
You're the man!
Don't be shy now.
Embrace your emotions, my flower,
and fly to my bazooka!
What?
No, thanks.
Don't worry, darling.
Even if you don't like what you see,
I'm filthy rich!
I said no, okay?
What?
How could you possibly refuse me?
No means no!
What?
I arranged such romantic settings.
What part of no don't you understand?
I think this has gone on long enough.
Huh?
Howdy-do.
Look, it doesn't matter how you slice it.
I don't think the lady's interested.
Rejection hurts, but what can you do?
You got a lot of nerve there, pal!
I don't think you grasp who you're dealing
with.
You're tangling with
the Moya Triad, ninja trio
that strikes fear in
the hearts of children!
Moya Triad?
Never heard of you.
Never heard of a Moya Triad?
You dare to mock us?
Who do you think you are?
Who, me?
The name's Kakashi Hatake.
I'm hardly worth mentioning.
So why'd you even bother?
No good scum!
You'll live to regret this!
You should know better than to meddle in a
man's quest for love.
Quest for love?
You mean stalking, don't you?
Hold your tongue!
All right, boys, time to dance.
Right!
Four, three, two, one!
Hustle!
Yeah!
Ow!
Hey,
come on, little help over here!
Seriously, I'm pretty scared of heights!
I'll take you back to the village.
Darling, where are you?
Are you just gonna leave us up here?
So anyway, that's how it all went down.
Don't gloat!
You're the one who lost!
So now we're gonna get payback for three
years ago.
The boss has only gotten stronger.
He'll crush that chump into dust if they
go to hell.
I'm not gonna let you go toe-to-toe!
The suspense is killing me!
You dingbat!
I'm not gonna stick my neck out like that!
Huh?
If I'm going to do this, it will be from
the shadows.
That's, uh, pretty dirty.
Ah-ho!
Oh, welcome!
My, my, my!
Welcome!
Yeah!
Oh!
Wow!
Oh, wow!
That looks good!
How lavish.
Take your time!
Enjoy your meal, Kakashi, for it will be
your last.
I've added a tasteless
and odorless narcotic to
your food that brings
on uncontrollable hiccups.
Dig in, my friend, and hiccup till you
die!
A fitting end for one such as you.
Hm?
What's the matter with you guys?
No one's picking up their chopsticks.
Oh, it's nothing.
Don't wait on us, Kakashi-sensei.
You go ahead and eat.
Actually, I'm kind of on a diet right now.
So that's how he wants to play it,
huh?
Well, I don't care what it takes.
That mask is coming off!
Oh, no!
My hand slipped!
Aaaaaaah!
Are you out of your mind?
Sorry about that.
My hand just slipped.
What do you mean your hand slipped?
Oh, no!
All our cooking!
How could he do such a thing?
Ugh!
Okay, what's our next move, guys?
Don't worry about it.
I think I have a plan.
What kind of plan?
Hm.
Not too shabby.
Way to come through, Sasuke.
Who wouldn't take their mask off in a hot
spring?
All right, you loser.
Zip your lip already.
Ah!
Hahahaha!
Tonight you breathe your last breath,
Kakashi.
I've coated this blow dart
with an elixir I concocted
that brings on wild and
uncontrollable laughter.
Hm?
Hahahaha!
You'll die laughing!
A fitting end for one such as you.
Oh, man.
I wanted to get a look, too.
But with these hot springs, I'm out of the
loop.
I wanna see.
Oh...
What's the holdup, Kakashi-sensei?
One sec.
I'm coming.
Hm?
I gotta see this.
This is it!
Here we go!
Oh, I can't see a thing!
Hm...
Phew!
It is hot in here... And I'm just
coming in for a minute... Ah!
You've gotta be kidding!
Hm?
What's up with you
two... Well, I'm getting in.
Ah...
Ahh.
Hahahaha!
Ah!
You escaped again!
What's going on?
This is killing me!
Just great!
What the heck was Kakashi-sensei thinking
back there?
Huh?
Oh man, I'm completely flushed.
Where did our claws go?!
Come back anytime now!
Thank you very much!
Safe journey, Cam!
We'll come back anytime!
Curse you, Kakashi Hatake!
I will be your doom!
It's a good thing we brought along a spare
set of clothes, huh boss?
Yeah, I wonder who took them anyway?
Alright, you've all got jobs to do.
You'd best get to work.
Dismissed.
I'm about out of guys.
I don't think my nerves can handle much
more of this.
I'm getting pretty fed up myself.
Yeah, me too.
That makes three of us.
Alright then, desperate times call for
desperate measures!
Desperate measures?
Why are we dressed like this?
Isn't it obvious?
We're posing as a trio of rogue ninja!
Where did you even get these things?
Look, let's not get bogged down in the
details.
Do you even have a plan?
Strip off the mask, by force if we have
to!
Let's do it!
Alright, Kakashi.
Boss, look!
Hey, Kakashi Hatake!
Huh?
What are the three of you up to?
What are you talking about?
We're just three wandering ninja!
It's not like we want to see what's behind
your mask or anything!
You idiot!
Don't say any more than you have to!
That's my suit!
Hey boss, it looks like you're not the only
one who wants to get revenge on Kakashi.
Now's our chance!
Let's do it!
Right!
Hold it!
Right there!
Kakashi, it's time you pay for your
transgressions.
And the price is death,
delivered in the form of
this elixir, which will make
you weep uncontrollably!
That's funny.
I was just wondering how long you fellas
were going to hide for.
And you finally decide to show yourselves.
First things first, though.
Sasuke, Sakura, Naruto...
Why on earth are you dressed like that?
Huh?
Uh, well, the
thing is... Oh boy!
We'd better come up with something fast!
You fools!
You fell right into our trap!
We've known all along you were targeting
Kakashi-sensei!
That's impossible!
Are you telling me that our machinations
were exposed from the very beginning?
Of course!
This was all just a ruse to lure you guys
out, and you fell for it!
Hook, line, and sinker!
So we were caught up in your web of
deception!
Crash!
We underestimated them because they were
kids!
No one filled me in on any of this.
Nice work, Sakura.
Well, I'm not sure I really get what's
going on around here, but... whatever.
Please forgive us!
Forgive us!
Words aren't going to help you,
kid.
This is just like three years ago all over
again!
We're swinging from a rope like an
oversized yo-yo!
You've got us all trussed up in the same
stupid rope!
Hey, by the way, who are you guys?
And he doesn't even remember who we are!
Hey, Kakashi-sensei!
Yeah?
What are you hiding under that mask?
What?
You want to know what's behind my mask?
Yeah!
You should have just said so in the first
place.
So does that mean you'll show us?
Sure, I don't mind.
What's the big deal?
Alright.
Is it limp lips?
Or buck teeth?
Or a tiny mouth?
Behind this mask...
Behind that mask...
...is another mask!
Pretty cool, huh?
Are you freaking kidding me?
What the hell kind of ending is that?
We've received intel on the thieves who
took the golden statue.
They're either on land on this forest
path...
...or they're sailing by boat and will
land somewhere in this area.
So, we'll split into two teams and wait
for them in both locations.
Now, to keep the teams balanced, I'll be
on one and you three will be on the other.
Hold on, what does that mean?
Are you saying that Sasuke needs all the
help he can get?
No, he means you.
I know I'm not up to your level yet,
but I doubt you need three on one team.
So, why don't you take Naruto off my
hands?
You subtract his skill from yours and
we'll be even.
Sasuke, is this just a clever ruse so that
you and I can be alone together?
Come on, you've got to be kidding!
Why would my skill subtract from his?
Simple, because you have nothing to add.
What?
Sasuke wants to be with me so much he
can't even breathe!
You're as annoying as he is.
Pay attention now.
I'll watch the pier and you three will
keep an eye on this path in the forest.
If the thieves appear, notify me right
away.
Do not underestimate them.
Our mission is to retrieve a stolen golden
statue.
We must proceed with the utmost caution.
If the thieves appear at my location,
I'll send a signal with this.
When this lightning barrel is tossed into
the air, it'll release a thunderbolt.
Once you verify that it went off, rush
straight to the location that it marks.
You better be careful with that.
I don't want to get zapped again.
Remember, you three are not to act on your
own.
Hmm...
It's the thieves!
You idiot!
Be careful with that treasure,
you hear me?
Yes, sorry, Boss Jaco!
Get it together!
Yes, sir!
The treasure's in that wicker box?
This is it.
This is my big chance!
You're amazing, Naruto!
You're so much cooler than Sasuke!
You really showed him up!
Huh?
Don't tell me he's planning the same
thing.
I'm not gonna lose to him!
What?
What is this?
Huh?
Damn it!
They took the treasure!
What do they think they're doing?
We're supposed to notify Kakashi-sensei
first!
There's another one!
You two, give me that treasure back!
No way!
Forget it!
Then take this!
Ah!
I'm not gonna lose it now!
Damn!
So the Hidden Leaf's coming after us,
huh?
Were those two the only ones with you?
I know that there must be more of you.
Yeah, that's why you tried to send that
signal to reveal our location.
It's pretty cool, isn't it?
Clearly, I'm a natural-born thief who's
rotten to the very core of this being.
So rotten, in fact, that as you can clearly
see, even my chakra has become new fowl.
Those two Frenzivers escaped downstream.
We'll split up and
search the river until we
find them, and then we'll
take back our treasure.
What do we do with her?
We'll bring her with us and keep her as a
hostage.
I can't believe they stole something as
ridiculous as this... this... teddy bear.
The thunderbolt.
The signal to warn Kakashi.
It didn't go off, did it?
Oh... no.
Maybe... Sakura couldn't release it.
You think Sakura... was captured?
What?
What is this?
What's going on?
We're stuck together.
Ready?
Pull!
Here we come!
Take this!
And...
And... And...
And... ... oh.
Why do I always end up kissing you?
You took the words right out of my mouth!
Don't worry, you'll see your friends soon
enough.
After they return the
treasure, I'll make sure that
you're all back together
again in the afterlife.
You're ninja, but even ninja become
helpless if their hands are bound.
Sasuke... Naruto... Sakura...
While we're stuck like this,
Sakura could be... Naruto!
Stop, you idiot!
Hang tight, Sakura!
I'm coming to save you right now!
Listen, just wait, you loser!
Just what the hell are you doing,
Sasuke?
I mean, don't you even care what happens
to Sakura?
Look, we will save her.
But we can't do anything when we're like
this.
Saving her no matter what stands in the
way is what a true friend would do!
I just... I don't want people to say that
I'm scum!
Who doesn't care about his friends!
Those ninja who abandon their friends are
even worse than scum.
Yeah, fine!
But joining up with Kakashi is still the
right move!
It'll increase her chances of survival!
Look, don't talk to me about her chances!
That just depends on how hard we work to
save her!
There's no way I'll let her die over this
stupid thing!
You idiot!
Naruto, stop it!
No, dammit!
Dammit!
But... someone who doesn't take his
mission seriously is scum too.
Yeah...
Gotta be.
You... what?
I said...
I gotta go take a leak!
Hey, what in the hell?
Oh, uh, okay, one-handed then.
What?
Cut it out!
Not so close!
You're gonna splash it on me!
Listen, I'm sorry, but if you gotta go,
you gotta go!
Just hold it!
I can't!
Knock it off!
Stop it!
Zip it up!
Huh?
Ah!
Don't get in my way, Naruto!
Are you kidding?
You're the one who's in my way!
Stop!
Give us back the treasure!
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You can't weave a sign like this,
idiot!
You need two hands!
It's like I said before, we don't have a
chance, even if they are weaker than we are!
I know that now!
Naruto!
Stop this!
No!
No way!
If you're not in, I'll cut my arm off,
then go!
I'm gonna beat this guy!
And then go and save Sakura!
Sakura!
You're always so reckless!
Alright, let's go!
Time to save Sakura!
If those guys came
this far, they'll probably
find us before we can
meet Kakashi-sensei.
If that's the case, it'll
be faster if we just make
this guy tell us where
Sakura is and save her first.
Huh?
Sasuke...
However, to succeed, we have to work
together perfectly.
Huh?
Got it!
I just remembered.
I gotta pee.
Me too.
What
do you mean, Sugoro still hasn't reported
back yet?
You know, I wonder...
You're wondering right!
We got him!
Sasuke!
Naruto!
There!
Hah!
That's right!
We're back and free at last!
Only a feudal lord's sister would own a
statue like that one.
And that's exactly what managed to pull us
apart.
So their hands are free now?
Here's our offer.
We'll let you have this back, in exchange
for our teammate.
Refuse and I'll pulverize every one of
you!
Trust me, that won't be a problem now that
my hands are free!
We're both ninja.
Surely you don't think mere robbers can
defeat us.
You can't.
Huh.
Tell me, why are you gritting your teeth
so hard?
You're sweating.
Your veins are practically popping out of
your skin.
Alright then.
If you're truly free, then come over here!
Come on!
Just as I thought.
Their hands are still fused.
There's nothing to fear.
Get him!
He called our bluff.
Then we have no choice.
Are you?
Naruto!
Right!
locked up.urd.
...Where, brother?
It means... They've within.
Lucky they're alive!
Can't change people in I just can't!
Even like this, we can take that guy.
Let's go!
Don't even think about it!
Fire style!
Shadowpaw jutsu!
No way!
A hand sign!
No.
Even if we could weave signs, we couldn't
infuse chakra like this, idiot.
Don't treat me like a fool!
But we do have a combination attack!
You what?
Pachinko jutsu!
Well,
maybe it can be melted down and recast.
Though that's a pretty big maybe.
Oh Sasuke, thank you!
What?
He didn't do it by himself, you know,
Sakura.
This is getting ridiculous!
Can't you do anything, Kakashi-sensei?
Look, that thief already told you guys.
It'll just crumble apart on its own in two
or three days.
If I have to put up with him that long,
I'll kill him!
I should be the one who's saying that!
Uh-oh.
I gotta go.
Again?
Yes, again.
And this time it's number two.
You gotta be kidding me!
Don't you dare, Naruto!
Come on, we already peed together,
what's the big deal?
This is so much worse!
Those who abandon their friends are worse
than scum.
These three overcome their differences so
easily.
Hm.
Okay... Alright, with that being said, our
mission is now over-we're all dismissed.
Already?
It's only 10 in the morning!
Our missions have been so boring!
When we gonna get an S rank mission,
come on?
Hm.
S rank?
Yeah right, a loser like you?
What you talking about?
H Yuko?
We're slip only Ganon.
I mean, remember?
I want something with more pizzazz,
more oomph, so...
There just aren't any missions.
Anyway, dismissed.
You heard him!
So, Sasuke, how about today,
the two of us... I'm going home.
Wait, just hold on a minute.
I know a 1S-rank mission the three of us
could actually do right now.
A mission that's failed again and again.
One that only we can pull off.
To see what Kakashi-sensei's face really
looks like.
Let's find out our target's best-kept
secret!
Do you even know what you're saying?
Listen, just forget about that.
It's impossible.
I mean, right, Sasuke?
This would be the perfect mission for a
day like today.
I couldn't agree more.
Sasuke!
How could you?
You betrayed me!
But what do we do?
Every single time we try this,
it never goes well.
Not to worry.
I already have a plan!
What is it?
Photographs!
If we go through every
single photo Kakashi-sensei is
in, there's bound to be at
least one without a mask!
Actually, I never told you this, but I
already checked them out once before.
And he has a mask on in every one!
The photo submitted to the Hokage for the
ninja registration form.
That should be a picture of him where he
isn't wearing a mask.
But of course, it's an extremely
classified top-secret document.
Getting your hands on it won't be an easy
task.
Who are you?
I'm Sakeya.
I'm a photographer.
I travel from east to west looking for
stories.
Not north or south!
Naruto, stop getting hung up on
insignificant details!
Well, anyway, I was on
the hunt for a scoop, and I
happened to overhear
your fascinating conversation.
He did hear us!
Let's get rid of him!
Ready?
Idiot!
This guy's right.
That is the regulation.
The ninja registration form photo must
show your face.
It's so obvious, but none of us even
thought about looking there before now.
So listen, do you think
you guys would let me
tag along with you
on this little adventure?
And why would you want to do that?
It's simple.
If I'm able to capture this
Kakashi guy without a mask on,
it'll be the biggest scoop
since the Leaf was established.
Even if it were to get hushed up, I'd
be sure to make a lot of money on this.
Oh!
Hey!
Hold on!
When you get the money, you gotta treat us
to ramen, promise?
I'll even throw in some gyoza.
Does that sound good?
Hm.
Now this is getting interesting.
I don't know, you guys.
Aw, yeah!
I'm getting excited about this!
This is where they store secret documents.
This'll be an infiltration mission.
Sukeya, you think you'll be able to keep
up?
I don't think it'll be a problem.
Before I became a photographer,
I was a rank-and-file ninja.
All right.
Let's get this mission started.
You're still not done, Sasuke?
Shut up.
Just hold on.
Can we switch places?
Just for a moment.
Wow!
It opened!
That's awesome!
So, Sukeya.
What division did you belong to before?
Oh, I was in the intel unit.
That reported to Lord Hokage.
Wait, he means the... Anbu.
Black Ops.
Eh?
Well, something's happened, and now I'm
retired.
Given your past, is it wise for you to be
doing this?
You'll be targeted by the Anbu.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be just fine.
Come on.
Let's go.
We have to search all these?
Let's hurry.
Found it.
This is it.
All right.
Let's open it up.
No way!
The moment is finally here!
Don't move.
We're taking you in.
Make a move and we'll assume you're
resisting.
And we may have to take you down.
Uh-oh.
I feel like I'm gonna sneeze.
Idiot.
Hold it in.
Damn it.
And we were so close, too.
Really.
An infiltration mission.
I know.
I'm really sorry about that.
I tried to stop them, but they insisted on
doing it.
What?
You jerk!
So right from the start, you planned on
blaming us if this failed.
They just wanted to see what your face
really looked like.
You're a former Anbu black ops,
right?
Honestly, it's ridiculous.
Who cares what I look like underneath this
mask anyway?
You've really got some nerve blaming us!
I thought it was pretty strange that you
wanted to join us.
You're skilled and a former Anbu,
so you could have easily done this alone.
I can't stand handsome guys who think they
can get away with awful things.
Sorry, sorry.
How about I make it up to you by helping
you photograph Kakashi's face?
Take advantage of my photography skills.
What?
You still wanna do this?
Why not?
Are you gonna give up already?
Uh, alright.
So what's your plan?
Let's go for Kakashi himself.
We'll lure him out to a meal, then
photograph him while he eats.
We already tried doing that a whole bunch
of times, but nothing we did ever worked.
Every single time, right at
the very moment when we'd
have a chance to see his
face, we'd get interrupted.
Well, with this multi-exposure camera I
built, I bet we can get at least one photo.
Sensei!
I need to talk to you about something very
important, you know?
What is it?
Uh...
Actually, why don't we eat some dumplings?
Dumplings while we talk!
Okay, I'm ready to go.
Well, alright.
Don't mind if I do.
Oh, hey, Naruto.
You guys out taking a little break,
too?
Don't bother us right now!
We're doing something really important!
Like what?
I was just about to find that out.
What?
He already ate them?
Hehehe.
But this time we got him on camera!
How can this be?
It's impossible!
Are you kidding?
Not a single one?
It feels like some divine powers at work
here.
Yeah, that's a shame.
Oh well, I guess this means...
we'll have to say that the mission... is
over and dismissed, huh?
Alright, I guess it's time
for me to be... Hey, Naruto!
Hm?
You want to tell me what's really going on
out here?
Oh, hey!
What's up, you guys?
H-Hikashi-sensei!
Huh?
I'm so glad you're here!
Because, you see, um, it's just that
over there's a... It's going to be alright.
But first, just calm down and tell me
what's wrong.
I think that a woman might have drowned
right over there on the riverbank!
What?
This is really not good.
Her pulse is very weak.
Yes!
Sakura did an awesome job!
Her medicines even fooled Takashi-sensei!
Alright, this calls for it.
Hehehe!
He definitely has to take his mask off
now!
This woman's in danger.
We can't waste any time.
We have to get her to the hospital right
away!
A has failed.
Understood.
Everyone switch to Plan B.
Skaia, please get into position.
Roger that.
Okay, he's coming our way now.
Just as Shikamaru predicted, he's gonna
pass by on his way to the hospital.
Everyone, get in position.
Huh?
Expansion jutsu!
Human boulder!
Row, row, row, row, row, row, row,
row, row, row, row!
row, row!
What are you doing?
I have to get this woman to...
Go!
Hidden Jutsu!
Beetle Spear!
Now!
Three, two, one, go!
Scatter!
Mine Transfer Jutsu!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit!
Look, you guys, I get
that you want to see
what I look like, but
we have a situation here.
She needs to get to the hospital as soon
as...
Shadow Possession Jutsu, now complete.
All right!
Sakeya, do it now!
It finally worked, Naruto.
Guess you get to have those ramen and
gyoza now.
Haha!
Hey guys, see that?
The plan actually worked!
Yeah, finally.
You should all be grateful to us.
The reason is because... Okay,
Kagashi-sensei, I hope you're ready!
Do it, Shikamaru!
It's time for the unveiling!
Wait, you guys, hold on!
Come on, why don't we just talk things
over, okay?
Hey, hold on a second.
Stop!
Just stop!
Let's all calm down.
I mean, having this remain as a mystery
makes it much more alluring, don't you think?
Ramen and Gyoza Ichiraku sound more
alluring to me.
You mean to tell me all of you were bribed
to do this?
That's checkmate.
Alright, now stop!
I mean, please, you guys, wait!
You're so annoying, Lee!
Please, spar with me, Netty!
What?
Hey, stop!
Don't interfere!
Seriously, come on already!
Enough is enough!
Hey!
Wait for me!
Sorry!
He was a shadow clone?
What the hell is going on here?
Was Kakashi-sensei onto us right from the
very start?
Well, it's too bad, but I really am
grateful to all of you.
No way!
We all had such an awesome time!
And it's actually because of you,
Sakeya!
So, thank you!
I better get going now.
Call me anytime if something comes up.
I really hope you get that scoop that you
wanted!
Of course!
It seems like they had a lot of fun...
If only the two of us stayed!
I don't know how you can claim that,
but you've been such quite a good friend!
And I'm actually very impressed by your
friendship!
It was quite a coincidence that Kiba
happened to show up at the dumpling shop.
Huh, who would have thought that all of
them would team up?
I think that something like this is good
for them.
At least every once in a while.
Yeah, but I gotta say, this really wore me
out.
It's tiring to use so many clones and
transformations.
It was a really close call with my mask
because everyone had such good teamwork.
Of course, even if they
did get the mask off,
there wouldn't have
been any real hard done.
Because I'm wearing a backup mask
underneath.
I still think food is the best way.
Yeah, it probably is our best chance.
But the problem is, how do we get
Kakashi-sensei to eat with us?
Bad timing!
Here they come!
Hey!
Excuse me.
Did you notice any trouble going on around
here?
Huh?
No, I didn't see anything at all.
Kakashi... I heard that he and his team
were causing a commotion around town.
Anyway, my apologies for stopping you.
It's okay.
Hey!
Uh, can I, uh, help you with something?
Don't I know you from somewhere?
Uh, no.
I don't think we've ever met before.
Really?
Okay then, well, excuse me.
See you later.
I could've sworn I met that guy somewhere
before.
Oh well, I guess it doesn't matter.
Besides,
I'm not a fool, you know?
I think I know what I'm doing.
This is the last time you'll ever get to
see me.
Come on, get up and get out of the car.
You'll be fine.
Kusui, can I talk to you?
Of course.
I'll be fine.
Okay.
See you.
It actually turned out to be a good
mission after all.
Plus, I have to say, their
teamwork has gotten much
better than it was during
the bell-snatching mission.
Well, I'll only be able to do this a
couple more times.
Don't cry, cause you're so right.
Don't try with fakes or fears,
cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry, cause you're so right.
Don't try with...